This is the place, huh?
（マイト･ガイ）ここか
Gaara is on the other side of this boulder.
（パックン）我愛羅があらはこの岩の中だ
It looks like they put up a barrier.
（ガイ）どうやら
結界が張られているな
What's the plan?
（テンテン）どうします？
Let's bust through!
（ロック･リー）突入しましょう
いや
No!
You're late, Kakashi.
遅かったな カカシ
Well, you see...
（はたけカカシ）いやいや
we got caught up in something
troublesome along the way.
途中 めんどくさいのに
からまれちゃって
Naruto! Sakura!
（リー）ナルト君 サクラさん
Kakashi... By troublesome,
you certainly don't mean me, do you?
（チヨ）カカシよ
（チヨ）めんどくさいのとは
わしのことでは あるまいな
Hey!
（うずまきナルト）押忍！
Naruto...
（日向ひゅうがネジ）ナルト…
さあて やるか？ カカシ
Now, shall we do this, Kakashi?
Yeah.
（カカシ）ああ
FORBIDDEN
Hang on, Gaara.
（ナルト）我愛羅 待ってろよ
♪～
～♪
Charge Tactic!
Button Hook Entry!!
It looks like there's
a large cavern inside, but...
（ネジ）中はかなり広い
空洞になっているようだが…
But...?
（リー）だが？
（ネジ）んっ…
I can't really see clearly
what's going on inside...
あまり はっきりとは
中の様子を捉えることができない
It looks like there are
several people inside...
何人かいるようだ
What about Gaara, Neji?
（ナルト）ネジ… 我愛羅は？
What's happening to Gaara?!
おい… 我愛羅は
どうなってるんだ！
Wait!
（ネジ）待て 今 探してる
I'm searching right now!
Neji!
（ナルト）ネジ！
（ネジ）こら
Hey!
ああっ…
Wh-What's...that...?
な… なんだ？ あれは
（ナルト）どうしたんだよ おい
What is it?
Hey! What's in there, Neji?!
何があるんだってばよ ネジ！
（ネジ）あっ…
Let go of me...
放せ
What was in there?
（春野はるのサクラ）何があったの？
口では説明しづらい
It's hard to explain in words...
（テンテン）ということは…
Which means...
Which means we just have to
check it out directly for ourselves, right?
（リー）ということは
直接 自分の目で確かめるしかない
というわけですね？
That makes things simple.
（ガイ）ならば話は早い
うう～ ああ～っ
クソがよお～！
A barrier, huh...?
結界か
It's getting noisy outside.
（暁のリーダー）
外が騒がしくなってきたな
（干柿ほしがき鬼鮫きさめ）
連中が到着したようですね
It appears they've arrived.
Which group? Hm?
（デイダラ）
どっちの連中だ うん？
鬼鮫の旦那が
足止めしていたほうか？
The group my man Kisame stalled?
それとも…
Or is it...
It's...both groups...
（ゼツ）これは両方だ
So they arrived at the same time, huh?
仲よく同時に ご到着か
However...
だが…
They were just a bit late...
残念 ちょっと遅かったな
It seems they've got another
Jinchuriki with them...
（サソリ）もう１人
人柱力がいるんだってな
フフフフフ…
Don't take it personally, Itachi.
悪く思うなよ イタチ
フッ フフ… ハハハ…
What's the plan?
（リー）どうします？
First, we have to
remove the barrier, Lee.
（ガイ）まずは結界を
外さなければならんな リーよ
How do we do that?
どうやって？
それには これがどんな結界なのか
見極める必要があるわね
We need to figure out
what kind of barrier it is, right?
Yeah.
ああ
All right. First, we need to find out
what type of barrier this is!
よーし 最初は
この結界の種類だな
Isn't that right, Kakashi!
カカシよ
Right.
（カカシ）ああ
FORBIDDEN
What does it look like to you?
どう見る？
（カカシ）これは五封結界ですね
This is...a Five-Seal Barrier.
（チヨ）うん 同感じゃ
I agree.
A Five-Seal Barrier?
五封結界…
（カカシ）この五封結界は
禁と書かれた札を
A Five-Seal Barrier is created by placing...
paper tags with "Forbidden" written
on them in five locations in the area.
近辺の５か所に貼り付けて
結界を作ってんだ
There's the Forbidden tag
here in front of us...
（カカシ）目の前にある禁の札と
ほかの４か所にある札
and tags in four other locations...
How can we remove them?
（ガイ）どうやれば外れる？
We can't remove the barrier
（カカシ）５か所に貼ってある札
その全てを同時に剥がさなければ
unless we remove the tags in
all five locations simultaneously.
結界は外れない
必ず同時でなければ いけないのね
It must be done simultaneously, huh?
That's right.
そうだ ５枚同時でなければ
結界は外れない
The barrier can't be removed unless
the five tags are removed simultaneously.
That's how it's been set up.
そういう仕組みだ
That tag there...
そこに１枚
And there are four others...
そのほかに４枚か
FORBIDDEN
んんっ
Then, where are the other four tags?!
じゃあ どこにあんだよ？
そのほかの４枚ってば
Neji.
（カカシ）ネジくん
分かってますよ
I know.
Byakugan!
白眼びゃくがん
見つけた
I found them!
Where are they, Neji?!
（ナルト）ネジ どこだ？
There's one on a boulder about
500 meters northeast of here...
（ネジ）ここから北東の方角
約500メートルの岩の上
The...second one...
（ネジ）２枚目は…
is on the trunk of a tree growing
along a riverbank
南南東に350メートルの
川岸に生えている木の幹
350 meters to the south-southeast...
The third one...
（カカシ）３枚目は…
is on a cliff about
650 meters to the northwest...
北西 約650メートルの岸壁
The last one...
（カカシ）最後は…
is in a forest a little less than
800 meters to the southwest...
南西 約800メートル弱の林の中
（カカシ）この４か所だ
Those are the four locations.
If so, then they are pretty far away.
（サクラ）だとすると
結構 距離があるわね
What will the signal be?
合図はどうするの？
（ガイ）それなら問題ない
No problem there!
その距離ならば
確か無線が届くはずだ
At that distance...
we should be able to use
wireless radios.
ハッ 無線か
Wireless radios, huh?!
I see.
（カカシ）なるほど
ほう
Okay, we'll all stay in communication
and find the tags with Neji's directions!
（ガイ）では ネジの指示を受けながら
相互連絡を取って札を見つける
（飛段ひだん）さてと
ぼちぼち引き上げるとするか
Now then. Shall we get going...?
It's starting to get noisy outside
外も騒がしくなってきたし
and we've got our mission
to complete, after all.
こっちもノルマを
果たさなきゃならないからな
（ゼツ）そのとおりだ
Exactly...
What shall we do with
the guys outside?
（角都かくず）外の連中はどうする？
（鬼鮫）まっ ここには
入ってこられるかどうかも
Well, we don't even know
if they can get in here...
分かりませんがね
（うちはイタチ）
やつらを甘く見るな
Don't underestimate them.
分かっているはずだ
You should know.
（鬼鮫）フッフフフ…
Well... I acknowledge
their brute strength, at least.
まあ バカ力だけは
認めてあげますがね
Sasori.
（暁のリーダー）サソリ
Deidara.
デイダラ
（デイダラ）うん？
You take care of the guys outside.
（暁のリーダー）外のヤツらは
お前たちで始末しておけ
I knew it would turn out like this...
やっぱ そうなるか うん
But take the Jinchuriki alive.
（暁のリーダー）ただし
人柱力は生け捕りにしろ
We know.
（サソリ）分かってる
Everyone else is dismissed.
（暁のリーダー）ほかは解散
Let's go.
（飛段）行くぞ
Right...
（角都）ああ
We'll be leaving, too...
（鬼鮫）それでは我々も
Itachi...
（サソリ）イタチ
九尾の人柱力は
一体どんな野郎だ？
What's the Nine-Tailed Jinchuriki like?
Tell him.
（暁のリーダー）教えてやれ
He'll be the first one to yell
and scream at you.
（イタチ）一番最初に
大声でどなってくるヤツが そうだ
（サソリ）ああ？ なんだそりゃ
What does that mean?
Doesn't he have any more
specific characteristics?
（デイダラ）もっとほかに
具体的な特徴はねえのか うん？
Oh my...
あら…
Well, that's about it...
（鬼鮫）では そういうことで
（サソリ）チッ
（鬼鮫）いいんですか？
あなたのノルマだったのでは？
You okay with that?
Wasn't he your  target?
Let's go.
（イタチ）行くぞ
Okay.
（鬼鮫）はい
We'll remove the tags in
the four surrounding locations.
（ガイ）周りの４か所の札は
俺たちが剥がす
スピードで競うなら
俺の隊のほうが速いからな
If this is a competition of speed,
our team will probably be faster, after all.
頼むってばよ
We're counting on you!
All right, you head for
the northwest forest, Lee!
（ガイ）よし
リーは北西の林へ向かえ
Yes, Guy Sensei!
はい ガイ先生
（ガイ）ネジは北東の岩を任せる
I leave the northeast boulder to you, Neji.
Roger.
了解した
そして テンテンは南南東だ
And you take the south-southeast, Tenten.
Understood.
（テンテン）分かったわ
北西の崖には俺が向かう
I'll head for the northwest cliff.
恐らくは１番剥がしにくい場所に
貼ってあるに違いないからな
I'm sure that one will be in
the location most difficult to remove.
（カカシ）周波数は？
What's the frequency?
１ ７ ４だ
174.
（カカシ）了解だ
Roger.
（リー）みなさん 聞こえますか？
Can you hear me guys?
（ガイ）きゃあ～
（テンテン）ううっ
（ネジ）ぐっ く…
リー！ マイク 感度上げすぎ！
Lee! You've got your microphone
turned up too high!
あっ
Oh!
（リー）申し訳ありません
I'm sorry!
（ガイ）クソ～
（ハウリング音）
（カカシ）うおお～
リー リーよ…
Lee... Lee...!
あっ
すみません
I'm sorry...
（テンテン）
無線 セッティング オーケー
My wireless radio settings are okay.
うん
（ネジ）こちらもオーケーだ
Mine are okay as well.
（ガイ）よーし ガイ班～
All right. Team Guy...
んん～
（ガイ）ん？
（リー）あっ はい
R-Right!
（ガイ）うん！
うん フフッ
んん～ んっ？
ぐ… ええっ
（ガイ）んっ！
はいはい
Okay, okay...
（ガイ）うん
フフフッ
んん～
うん？
んん～っ んん～っ
んん んん？ うん
うう～ん？
うう～ん！
んん～っ！
んっ フッ
（手が当たる音）
（ガイ）うん
ハハハハハッ
青春フルパワーで
With the full power of youth!
- Fight!
-Yeah!
（ガイ）ファイト！
（リー）オー！
- Fight!
- Yeah!
（ガイ）ファイト！
（リー）オー！
- Fight! Fight!
- Yeah! Yeah!
（ガイ）ファイト！
（リー）オー！
（ガイ）おまけにファイト！
- And an extra fight!
- Yeah!
（ガイ）散さん！
Scatter!
いいなあ いいな あのノリ
How cool. What cool enthusiasm!
なあ なあ 俺たちも…
Hey guys, let's do that, too...!
死んでも嫌
I'd rather die...
（カカシ）だな
Right...
ぼけ
You fool...!
（ナルト）ガクッ
Well, it's time for me to get going.
じゃあ そろそろ拙者は消えるか
いても邪魔にはなっても
役には立たんからな
There's no reason for me to be here
if I'll just be in the way.
（カカシ）パックン ご苦労ね
Good work, Pakkun.
では これにてドロン
Okay, I'm gone...
（暁のリーダー）あとは任せるぞ
I leave the rest to you.
（サソリ）ああ
Right...
（デイダラ）分かってる うん
We got it...
I'll be waiting to hear from you.
（暁のリーダー）連絡を待つ
作戦を確認する
Verifying operation.
ガイ班の４人は札を見つけたら
その場で待機
The four members of Team Guy are
to stand by once they find their tags!
After all members have
reached their positions...
全員が配置に着いたところで
俺の合図で 一斉に剥がす
we'll remove the tags
all at once on my signal!
いいな？
Got it?!
はい
Yes!
（ガイ）むろん
カカシ班も同時に剥がす
Of course, Team Kakashi will remove
their tags simultaneously as well.
これで五封結界は外れる
With this, the Five-Seal Barrier
will be removed.
（カカシ）結界が外れると同時に
サクラが入口の岩を破壊
The moment the barrier is removed...
Sakura will destroy the boulder
at the entrance.
That will be our signal to break inside...
and recover Gaara.
それを合図に内部に突入
我愛羅君を奪還する
Gaara...
（ナルト）我愛羅…
（デイダラ）う～ん 遅いな うん
They're late...
来るならとっとと
来てもらいたいもんだが うん？
I wish they'd just hurry up
and get here...
どうした？ サソリの旦那
What's wrong, my man Sasori?
待たされんのは
嫌いなんじゃなかったのか？
I thought you didn't like
to be kept waiting.
（サソリ）ああ 大嫌いさ
Yeah... I hate it...
Sasori...
（チヨ）サソリ…
まさか… こんな日が
やって来ようとはな
I never thought...
a day like this would come...
（ネジ）こちらネジ 配置に着いた
This is Neji. I'm in position.
（ガイ）こちらも発見した
まもなく到着する
I've found mine, too!
I'll be arriving soon.
（テンテン）こっちもあった
I've got mine, too!
（リー）ネジ…
Neji!
分かってる
I know!
白眼！
Byakugan!
もう少し南だ
A little further south!
A little further...
All right, it's right there!
もう少し… よし そこだ
（リー）オーケーです ありました
Okay! I found it!
こちら リー 配置に着きました
This is Lee! I'm in position!
カカシよ そっちはどうだ？
Kakashi, how's it going there?
（カカシ）いつでもいいぞ
We're ready when you are.
突入方法は
ボタンフックエントリー
We'll break in using
the Button Hook Entry.
（チヨ）うん
分かってるってばよ
ええ
よーし みんな
１ ２ ３で札を剥がすぞ
（ガイ）いくぞ！
１…
２…
３！
（カカシ）サクラ！
（サクラ）はい！
だああ～！
ハッ！
（ガイ）よーし
うまくいったようだな
んっ？
（テンテン）はあっ
（リー）あ… あれは…
おっ
あっ
（カカシ）遅かったか
（チヨ）うう…
（チヨ）サソリ…
さて どいつが人柱力かな？
クッ ク…
てんめえら ぶっ潰す！
（サソリ）“１番最初に
大声でどなってくるヤツ”
あいつか
どうやらそうみたいだな うん
♪～
～♪
さて 取り出しますは
どこにでもある巻物
ところが３つ数えると
ここからでっかい手裏剣が…
ちょ～っと
勝手に人の芸 取んないでよ
うるせえ！ こっちも
演芸大会に向けて練習してんだよ！
なんですって！
こら くだらん争いをするな
このわしが
とっておきの芸を教えてやる
見よ 華麗なる空中クナイ
うわあ クナイが浮いてる
特別に300両で教えてやるな
いや それ
傀儡くぐつ師じゃなきゃできねえし
次回「罠トラップ作動！
ガイ班の敵」
（デイダラ）鬼鮫の旦那
（鬼鮫）なんです？
旦那と組んでるイタチってのは
どんなヤツなんだい？
そうですねえ
イタチさんは
あの うちは一族の出身で
火遁の術を得意としていますが
何より恐ろしいのが
万華鏡写輪眼まんげきょうしゃりんがんです
（デイダラ）なんだい？ そりゃ
（鬼鮫）
強力な催眠眼と洞察眼を併せ持ち
天照あまてらすや月詠つくよみといった
高等忍術を華網にする究極瞳術どうじゅつです
なかなか芸術的な術を
使うじゃねえか うん
では １つ問題を出しましょう
（鬼鮫）
イタチさんの
写輪眼がどれか...
分かりますか？
正解はＡです
（デイダラ）顔もイケてるし
こりゃ旦那と違ってモテそうだな
あっ どうかしたか？
どうせ私は色物です
（デイダラ）案外
気にしてたんだな